<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2016 Jiri Eischmann <eischmann@redhat.com> -->
<!-- Copyright 2019 Evgeny Sinelnikov <sin@altlinux.org> -->
<application>
	<id type="desktop">mediawriter.desktop</id>
	<project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
	<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
	<name>ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="bg">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="ca">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="cs">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="da">ALT-medieskriver</name>
	<name xml:lang="de">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="es">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="fi">ALT-median luontityökalu</name>
	<name xml:lang="fr">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="fur">Scritôr Supuarts di ALT</name>
	<name xml:lang="he">כותב המדיה של ALT</name>
	<name xml:lang="hu">ALT médiaíró</name>
	<name xml:lang="id">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="it">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="ko">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="nl">ALT mediaschrijver</name>
	<name xml:lang="pl">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="pt">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="pt-BR">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="ru">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="sk">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="sq">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="sr">ALT Писач Медија</name>
	<name xml:lang="sv">ALT Mediaskrivare</name>
	<name xml:lang="tr">ALT Ortam Yazıcı</name>
	<name xml:lang="uk">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="zh-CN">ALT Media Writer</name>
	<name xml:lang="zh-TW">ALT 媒體寫入器</name>
	<summary>A tool to create a live USB drive with an edition of ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="bg">Инструмент за създаване на USB устройство с живо издание на ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ca">Una eina per a la creació d'una unitat USB autònoma amb una edició de ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro vytváření živých USB disků s některou z edicí ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="da">Et værktøj til at oprette et live-USB-drev med en udgave af ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="de">Ein Werkzeug, um einen Live-USB-Datenträger mit einer Ausgabe von ALT zu erzeugen</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="es">Una herramienta para crear USB vivos con una edición de ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fi">Luo USB-muistitikku, jolta voi käynnistää jonkin ALTn version</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fr">Un outil pour créer un disque USB live avec une édition de ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="fur">Un strument par creâ une unitât USB Live cuntune edizion di ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="he">כלי ליצירת כונן USB חי עם מהדורה של ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="hu">Egy eszköz indítható live USB meghajtó készítéséhez a ALT egy változatával.</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="id">Alat untuk menciptakan drive USB live dengan suatu edisi ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="it">Uno strumento per creare dispositivi live USB con una edizione di ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ko">ALT 에디션으로 라이브 USB 드라이브를 생성하는 도구</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="nl">Een hulpmiddel om een live-USB-drive te maken met een editie van ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie do tworzenia dysków USB typu Live z ALTą</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Ferramenta para criar um dispositivo live USB com uma edição do ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ru">Инструмент для создания live USB-диска с  вариантом ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sk">Nástroj na vytváranie live USB diskov s niektorou edíciou ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sq">Një mjet për krijim diskthi USB live me një version ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sr">Алатка за стварање живих УСБ уређаја са издањима ALT-е</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="sv">Ett verktyg för att skapa en live-USB-enhet med en utgåva av ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="ta">ஃபெடோரா பதிப்புடன் வரும் நேரடி இயக்கக USB வட்டை உருவாக்கும் ஒரு கருவி.</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="tr">ALT sürümünü içeren canlı USB aygıtı yaratmanızı sağlayan araç</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="uk">Інструмент для створення портативних дисків USB із редакцією ALT</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="zh-CN">一个用来创建 Live USB 启动盘的 ALT 版工具</summary>
	<summary xml:lang="zh-TW">為各種 ALT 版本製作 Live USB 裝置的工具</summary>
	<description>
		<p>A tool to create a bootable live USB drive with an edition of ALT. Not only can ALT Media Writer write an image to your flash drive, it can also download it for you. It offers official editions (Server, Workstation), ALT starterkits (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), and ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). It provides basic information about each of them to help you make the right choice.</p>
		<p xml:lang="bg">Инструмент за създаване на зареждащо живо USB устройство с ALT. ALT Media Writer записва образ на Вашия флаш диск, но също може и да го свали вместо Вас. Той предлага основните предназначения (Server, Workstation), ALT разновидности (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) и ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Програмата предоставя основна информация за всяка от версиите, за да Ви помогне да направите правилния избор.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ca">Una eina per crear una unitat USB autònoma d'arrencada amb una edició de ALT. ALT Media Writer no només pot escriure una imatge en la vostra unitat flash, també pot baixar-la. Ofereix les edicions oficials (Server i Workstation), els spins de ALT (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), i els starterkits de ALT (Rescue, Builder, ...). Proporciona la informació bàsica sobre cada un d'ells per ajudar a prendre la decisió correcta.</p>
		<p xml:lang="cs">Nástroj pro vytváření živých USB disků s některou z edicí ALT. Nejen, že ALT Media Writer zapíše obraz na váš disk, ale také ho pro vás stáhne. Nabízí oficiální vydání (Server, Workstation), Spiny ALT (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) a ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Obsahuje základní informace o každém z nich, aby pro vás bylo snažší udělat správnou volbu.</p>
		<p xml:lang="da">Et værktøj til at oprette et opstartsbart live-USB-drev med en udgave af ALT. ALT-medieskriver kan ikke blot skrive et aftryk til dit flash-drev, den kan også downloade det for dig. Den tilbyder officielle udgaver (Server, Workstation), ALT-spins (KDE Plasma-skrivebord, Xfce-skrivebord, Cinnamon-skrivebord, ...) og ALT regulare (rescue, builder, ...). Den giver grundlæggende information om hver af dem for at hjælpe dig med at træffe det rigtige valg.</p>
		<p xml:lang="de">Ein Werkzeug, um einen bootfähigen Live-USB-Datenträger mit einer Ausgabe von ALT zu erzeugen. ALT Media Writer kann nicht nur ein Abbild auf einen Flash-Datenträger schreiben, sondern auch für Sie herunterladen. Es werden offizielle Ausgaben angeboten (Server, Workstation), ALT starterkits (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop …) und ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder, …). Grundlegende Informationen zu jeder Ausgabe werden angezeigt, um Ihnen bei der Auswahl zu helfen.</p>
		<p xml:lang="es">Una herramienta para crear un USB vivo de arranque con una versión de ALT. ALT Media Writer no solamente escribe una imagen en su disco portátil, sino que además puede descargarla si no la tiene. Ofrece las versiones oficiales (Servidor, Estación de Trabajo), Ediciones especiales (Escritorio KDE Plasma, Escritorio Xfce, Escritorio Cinnamon...), y ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Proporciona información básica de cada una de ellas para ayudarle a elegir la más conveniente.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fi">Ohjelma, jolla voi luoda USB-muistilta käynnistettävän ALT. Luontityökalu osaa ladata levykuvan ja kirjoittaa sen USB-muistille. Tarjolla ovat viralliset editiot (Server ja Workstation), ALT starter (mm. Xfce-, Cinnamon- ja KDE Plasma -työpöydät) sekä ALT starterkits -julkaisut (mm. design-ohjelmistot ja turvallisuuslaboratorio). Valinnan avuksi niistä jokaisesta kerrotaan lyhyesti.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fr">Un outil pour créer une disque USB live avec une version de ALT. Non seulement ALT Media Writer peut écrire une image sur votre disque USB, mais il peut aussi la télécharger pour vous. Il offre les éditions officielles (Server, Workstation), les ALT starterkits (environnements KDE Plasma, Xfce, Cinnamon…) et les ALT Labs (Design Suite, Security Lab…). Il fournit des informations de base sur chacune de ces options pour vous permettre de faire le bon choix.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fur">Un strument par creâ une unitât USB Live inviabile cuntune edizion di ALT. Scritor Supuarts di ALT al pues no dome scrivi une imagjin su calvute, al pues ancje discjariâtile. Al ufrìs edizions uficiâi (Servidôr,Workstation), ALT starterkits (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) e ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Al furnìs informazions di base su ogniune di lôr par fâti sielzi ben.</p>
		<p xml:lang="he">כלי ליצירת כונן USB חי עם מהדורת ALT. לא בלבד שכותב המדיה של ALT מסוגל לכתוב תמונה אל כונן ההבזק, הוא יכול גם להורידה. מציע מהדורות רשמיות (Server, Workstation), הסבות ALT (שולחן עבודה KDE Plasma, שולחן עבודה Xfce, שולחן עבודה Cinnamon,...), ומעבדות ALT (ערכת עיצוב, מעבדת אבטחה). מספק מידע בסיסי על אודות כל אחד מהם לעזרה בבחירה הנכונה.</p>
		<p xml:lang="hu">Egy eszköz indítható live USB meghajtó készítéséhez a ALT egy változatával. A ALT médiaíró nem csak ki tudja írni a lemezképet, hanem le is tudja tölteni azt. A hivatalos, támogatott verziókat (Server, Workstation), a ALT Starter (KDE Plasma Desktop, XFCE Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), és a ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder, …) lemezképeit nyújtja. Alapinformációkat is nyújt mindegyikről, hogy helyesen választhasson.</p>
		<p xml:lang="id">Alat untuk menciptakan drive USB live yang dapat di-boot dengan suatu edisi ALT. ALT Media Writer tidak hanya dapat menulis image ke flash disk Anda, itu juga dapat mengunduhkan untuk Anda. Menawarkan edisi resmi (Server, Workstation), ALT starterkits (Desktop KDE Plasma, Desktop Xfce, Desktop Cinnamon, ...), dan ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder, ...). Menyediakan informasi dasar tentang masing-masing edisi untuk membantu Anda membuat pilihan yang benar.</p>
		<p xml:lang="it">Uno strumento per creare dispositivi live USB con una edizione di ALT. Non solo ALT Media Writer è in grado di scrivere immagini su chiavi USB, ma anche di effettuarne il download. Mette a disposizione le edizioni ufficiali (Server, Workstation), le starter di ALT (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), e le edizioni ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Fornisce inoltre informazioni di base su ciascuna di esse per aiutarvi a fare la scelta giusta.</p>
		<p xml:lang="nl">Een hulpmiddel om een opstartbare live-USB-drive te maken met een oplage van ALT. ALT mediaschrijver kan niet alleen een image naar je flash drive schrijven, maar kan deze ook voor je downloaden. Het biedt officiële edities aan (Server, Workstation), ALT starterkits (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), en ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Het biedt basis informatie over elke editie aan om je de juiste keuze te laten maken.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pl">Narzędzie do tworzenia dysków USB typu Live z ALTą. ALT Media Writer może zapisywać obrazy na dyskach USB i je pobierać. Oferuje oficjalne edycje (Server, Workstation), dodatkowe obrazy (KDE Plasma, Xfce, Cinnamon…) i obrazy z ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder…). Dostarcza podstawowe informacje o obrazach, aby pomóc dokonać właściwego wyboru.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pt">Uma ferramenta para criar dispositivos USB inicializáveis com uma edição do ALT. Ela não somente pode gravar imagens em seu dispositivo USB, mas também pode baixá-las para você. Ela oferece edições oficiais (Server, Workstation), starters do ALT (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), e ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Ela fornece informações básicas sobre cada uma delas para ajudá-lo a fazer a escolha certa.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pt-BR">Uma ferramenta para criar dispositivos inicializáveis USB live com uma edição do ALT. Ela não somente pode gravar imagens em seu dispositivo USB, mas também pode baixá-las para você. Ela oferece edições oficiais (Server, Workstation), starters do ALT (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...), e ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Ela fornece informações básicas sobre cada uma delas para ajudá-lo a fazer a escolha certa.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ru">Инструмент для создания загрузочных live USB-дисков с вариантом ALT. ALT Media Writer может не только записать образ на флэш-диск, но и загрузить его. Предлагаются официальные версии (Server, Workstation), сборки ALT (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) и ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Предоставляется основная информация по каждому из них, помогающая сделать правильный выбор.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sk">Nástroj na vytváranie spúšťateľných live USB diskov s niektorou edíciou ALT. ALT Media Writer dokáže nielen zapísať obraz na váš USB kľúč, ale ho pre vás aj stiahnuť. Ponúka oficiálne edície (Server, Workstation), ALT starter (Pracovné prostredie KDE, Xfce, Cinnamon, ...) a ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder, ...). Poskytuje taktiež základné informácie o každej edícii, aby ste si mohli vybrať tú správnu.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sq">Një mjet për krijim diskthi USB live me një version ALT. ALT Media Writer jo vetëm që mund të shkruajë një pamje te diskthi juaj, mundet edhe ta shkarkojë atë për ju. Ju ofron versione zyrtare (Server, Workstation), degëzime ALT(Desktop KDE Plasma, Desktop Xfce, Desktop Cinnamon,…), dhe ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Furnizon të dhëna bazë rreth secilit prej tyre për t’ju ndihmuar të bëni zgjedhjen e duhur.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sr">Алатка за стварање подизних, живих УСБ уређаја са издањима ALT-е. Не само што ALT Писач Медија може писати слике на ваш флеш уређај, он их такође може преузети уместо вас. Пружа званична издања (за сервере, радне станице), ALT стартовые  (КДЕ Плазма окружење, Xfce окружење, Цинамон окружење,...) и ALT регулярные (Rescue, Builder,...). Такође пружа основне податке о сваком од издања и тиме вам помаже да направите добар избор.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sv">Ett verktyg för att skapa en startbar live-USB-enhet med en utgåva av ALT.  ALT Mediaskrivare kan inte bara skriva en avbild till din flash-enhet, den kan hämta den åt dig också.  Den erbjuder officiella utgåvor (Server, Workstation), ALTstarter (KDE Plasma-skrivbord, Xfce-skrivbord, Cinnamon-skrivbord, …), och ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder, …).  Det erbjuder grundläggande information om var och en av dem för att hjälpa dig välja rätt.</p>
		<p xml:lang="tr">Bir ALT sürümünü içeren canlı USB aygıtı yaratmanızı sağlayan bu araçla yalnızca görüntünün aygıtınıza yazılmasını değil aynı zamanda sizin için indirilmesini de sağlayabilirsiniz. Resmi sürümlerin (Sunucu, Masaüstü) yanı sıra ALT seçkilerini (KDE Plasma Masaüstü, Xfce masaüstü, Cinnamon Masaüstü...) ve ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder...) da indirebilir ve doğru seçimi yapmanızı sağlayacak temel bilgileri bulabilirsiniz.</p>
		<p xml:lang="uk">Інструмент для створення придатних до завантаження записів портативної системи ALT на носіях USB. ALT Media Writer може не лише записувати образи на вашу флешку, але отримувати ці образи з інтернету. Програма запропонує вам офіційні випуски (Server, Workstation), ALT starterkits (KDE Plasma Desktop, Xfce Desktop, Cinnamon Desktop,...) та випуски ALT regulars (Rescue, Builder,...). Вона надає основну інформацію щодо кожного з образів, що допоможе вам зробити правильний вибір.</p>
		<p>ALT Media Writer can also write other bootable ISOs loaded from your local disk, but keep in mind that it's only tested with ALT images.</p>
		<p xml:lang="bg">ALT Media Writer също може да записва други зареждащи ISO образи, заредени от твърдия Ви диск, но имайте предвид, че това е тествано само с образи на ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ca">ALT Media Writer també pot escriure altres ISO d'arrencada des del vostre disc local, però tingueu present que només s'ha provat amb les imatges de ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="cs">ALT Media Writer také dokáže zapsat jiné bootovatelné ISO obrazy z vašeho disku, ale mějte na paměti, že byl testovaný pouze s obrazy ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="da">ALT-medieskriver kan også skrive andre opstartsbare ISO'er indlæst fra din lokale disk, men husk på at den kun er testet med ALT-aftryk.</p>
		<p xml:lang="de">ALT Media Writer kann außerdem mit bootfähigen ISO-Abbildern von Ihrer Festplatte umgehen. Bitte bedenken Sie jedoch, dass das Programm nur mit ALT-Abbildern getestet wurde.</p>
		<p xml:lang="es">ALT Media Writer también puede escribir otras ISOs de arranque que tenga en su disco duro, pero tenga en cuenta que solo se prueba con imágenes de ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fi">ALT-median luontityökalulla voi kirjoittaa USB:lle myös muita ISO-tiedostoja, mutta työkalua on testattu vain ALTn levykuvilla.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fr">ALT Media Writer peut aussi écrire d’autres images ISO amorçables chargées depuis votre disque local, mais sachez bien qu’il n’a été testé qu’avec les images de ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="fur">Scritôr Supuarts di ALT al pues ancje scrivi altris ISO inviabilis, cjariadis sul disc fis locâl, ma ten iniments che al è stât provât dome cun lis imagjins di ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="he">כותב המדיה של ALT מסוגל גם לכתוב דמויות ISO ניתנות לאתחול אחרות מהכונן המקומי, אך מוטב לזכור שהוא נבדק רק עם דמויות של ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="hu">A ALT médiaíró képes más indítható ISO-kat is kiírni a helyi lemezéről, de tartsa észben, hogy az alkalmazás csak ALT lemezképekkel lett tesztelve.</p>
		<p xml:lang="id">ALT Media Writer juga dapat menulis ISO yang dapat di-boot lain dari disk lokal Anda, tapi ingatlah bahwa ini hanya diuji untuk image ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="it">ALT Media Writer può inoltre creare altre ISO avviabili da immagini caricate dai dischi locali, ma va tenuto presente che è testato solo con le immagini ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="nl">ALT mediaschrijver kan ook andere opstartbare ISO's schrijven die geladen zijn vanaf je lokale schijf, maar denk eraan dat dit alleen getest is voor ALT images.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pl">ALT Media Writer może także zapisywać inne startowe pliki ISO z lokalnego dysku, ale należy pamiętać, że jest testowany tylko z obrazami ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pt">O ALT Media Writer também consegue gravar outros ISOs carregados a partir do seu disco local, mas tenha em atenção que apenas foi testado com imagens do ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="pt-BR">O ALT Media Writer também pode criar outras ISO inicializáveis a partir de seu disco local, mas tenha consciência de que isso só foi testado com as imagens do ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="ru">ALT Media Writer может записать и другие загрузочные ISO-файлы, которые берутся с вашего локального диска, но имейте в виду, что он проверен только с образами ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sk">ALT Media Writer umožňuje tiež zapísať iné spustiteľné ISO obrazy z vášho disku. Nezabudnite však, že bol testovaný iba s obrazmi ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sq">ALT Media Writer mund të shkruajë edhe ISO të tjera të nisshme të ngarkuara mga disku juaj vendor, por mos harroni se është provuar vetëm me pamje ALT.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sr">ALT Писач Медија такође може писати друге подизне ISO-е учитане са вашег локалног диска али знајте да се испробава само са ALT сликама система.</p>
		<p xml:lang="sv">ALT Mediaskrivare kan även skriva andra startbara ISO:er som hämtas från din lokala disk, men kom ihåg att den bara har testats med ALTavbilder.</p>
		<p xml:lang="tr">ALT Ortam Yazıcı aygıtınızda yer alan önyüklenebilen diğer ISO görüntülerinin yazılmasında da kullanılabilir ama aracın yalnızca ALT görüntüleri ile denendiğini lütfen aklınızda bulundurun.</p>
		<p xml:lang="uk">ALT Media Writer можна також скористатися для запису інших придатних до завантаження образів ISO з локального диска, але слід мати на увазі, що тестування програми виконувалося лише для образів ALT.</p>
	</description>
	<keywords>
        <keyword>iso</keyword>
        <keyword>alt</keyword>
        <keyword>altlinux</keyword>
        <keyword>usb</keyword>
        <keyword>writer</keyword>
        <keyword>live</keyword>
        <keyword>spin</keyword>
        <keyword>creator</keyword>
        <keyword>media</keyword>
    </keywords>
	<url type="homepage">https://github.com/altlinux/MediaWriter</url>
	<screenshots>
		<screenshot type="default">https://github.com/altlinux/MediaWriter/raw/master/dist/screenshots/expanded.png</screenshot>
		<screenshot>https://github.com/altlinux/MediaWriter/raw/master/dist/screenshots/details.png</screenshot>
	</screenshots>
	<update_contact>sin@altlinux.org</update_contact>
</application>
